<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Sports</string>
    <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->
    <string name="list_fragment_label">Sports</string>
    <string name="detail_fragment_label">Sport Info</string>

    <string name="baseball">Baseball</string>
    <string name="badminton">Badminton</string>
    <string name="basketball">Basketball</string>
    <string name="bowling">Bowling</string>
    <string name="cycling">Cycling</string>
    <string name="golf">Golf</string>
    <string name="running">Running</string>
    <string name="soccer">Soccer</string>
    <string name="swimming">Swimming</string>
    <string name="table_tennis">Table Tennis</string>
    <string name="tennis">Tennis</string>

    <string name="sports_list_baseball">Baseball is a classic sport steeped in tradition, often referred to as "America's pastime.</string>
    <string name="sports_list_badminton">Badminton is a high-speed racket sport that combines agility, precision, and endurance.</string>
    <string name="sports_list_basketball">Basketball is a dynamic and fast-paced sport that requires skill, strategy, and teamwork.</string>
    <string name="sports_list_bowling">Bowling is a precision-based sport that involves rolling a heavy ball down a lane to knock over pins arranged in a triangular formation.</string>
    <string name="sports_list_cycling">Cycling is a versatile and enduring sport that emphasizes endurance, speed, and precision.</string>
    <string name="sports_list_golf">Golf is a sport of precision, patience, and strategy.</string>
    <string name="sports_list_running">Running is one of the most accessible and universal forms of exercise and competition.</string>
    <string name="sports_list_soccer">Soccer, also known as football, is the world’s most popular sport, captivating billions of fans.</string>
    <string name="sports_list_swimming">Swimming is a versatile and demanding sport that tests endurance, speed, and technique.</string>
    <string name="sports_list_table_tennis">Table tennis, also known as ping-pong, is a fast-paced racket sport played on a rectangular table divided by a net.</string>
    <string name="sports_list_tennis">Tennis is a sport of precision, power, and strategy, played between two players (singles) or two teams of two (doubles).</string>

    <string name="sport_detail_baseball">Baseball is a classic sport steeped in tradition, often referred to as \"America\'s pastime.\" Played between two teams of nine players, the objective
        is to score runs by hitting a ball with a bat and running through a series of bases arranged in a diamond shape. Each team alternates between
        batting and fielding, with the fielding team aiming to prevent the batting team from scoring by catching the ball or tagging runners out.
        \n\nThe sport requires a combination of physical skill and strategic thinking. Batters must possess excellent hand-eye coordination to hit the ball,
        while pitchers use a variety of throws, like fastballs and curveballs, to challenge their opponents. Fielders need agility and precision to catch
        balls and make accurate throws to tag out runners. The game is structured in nine innings, with each inning offering opportunities for strategic
        plays.
        \n\nBaseball\'s charm lies in its blend of individual brilliance and teamwork. Iconic players like Babe Ruth and Jackie Robinson have left a lasting
        legacy, and major leagues such as MLB attract millions of fans annually. With its rich history, compelling rivalries, and timeless appeal, baseball
        continues to captivate audiences worldwide.</string>
    <string name="sport_detail_badminton">Badminton is a high-speed racket sport that combines agility, precision, and endurance. Played on a rectangular court divided by a net, the
        objective is to hit a shuttlecock over the net and land it in the opponent\’s court. Matches are played as singles or doubles, and players must
        rely on quick reflexes and tactical gameplay to outsmart their opponents.
        \n\nWhat sets badminton apart is the speed and trajectory of the shuttlecock, which can travel at over 300 km/h during professional games. Players need to
        master a variety of shots, including smashes, drops, and clears, to dominate the court. The sport demands exceptional footwork and stamina, as
        rallies often involve rapid changes in direction.
        \n\nBadminton is particularly popular in countries like China, Indonesia, and Denmark, where it enjoys a rich history and strong competitive culture. It is
        also a prominent Olympic sport, attracting millions of viewers globally. The sport\'s blend of physical intensity and strategic depth makes it a
        thrilling experience for both players and spectators.</string>
    <string name="sport_detail_basketball">Basketball is a dynamic and fast-paced sport that requires skill, strategy, and teamwork. Played on a rectangular court with a hoop at each end,
        the objective of the game is to score points by shooting the ball through the opposing team’s hoop. A standard basketball game is played between
        two teams of five players each, and the game is divided into four quarters. Players need agility, precision, and quick decision-making to
        outmaneuver their opponents and execute effective plays.
        \n\nThe game offers a blend of athleticism and strategy. Dribbling, passing, and shooting are essential skills, while defensive maneuvers like blocking
        and stealing add depth to the game. Basketball is not just about individual brilliance but also about how players synchronize their actions as a
        team. From setting screens to executing pick-and-rolls, teamwork is vital to success.
        \n\nGlobally popular, basketball has produced legendary athletes like Michael Jordan, LeBron James, and Kobe Bryant, who have become cultural icons.
        The sport is played at various levels, from street courts to professional leagues like the NBA. Its appeal lies in its simplicity and accessibility,
        making it a favorite among players and fans worldwide.</string>
    <string name="sport_detail_cycling">Cycling is a versatile and enduring sport that emphasizes endurance, speed, and precision. Whether on the road, track, or trails, cycling offers
        a unique blend of physical challenge and exploration. Competitive cycling includes road races, time trials, and mountain biking, each requiring
        specialized skills and equipment.
        \n\nEndurance and strategy are key in cycling, particularly in long-distance events like the Tour de France. Riders must conserve energy, draft behind
        others, and strategically time their efforts to outperform opponents. In track cycling, explosive speed and aerodynamics are crucial for success
        in events like sprints and pursuit races.
        \n\nBeyond competition, cycling is a popular recreational activity and an eco-friendly mode of transport. It promotes cardiovascular health, builds muscle
        strength, and provides a sense of freedom. With its wide-ranging appeal and global reach, cycling continues to inspire both athletes and casual
        enthusiasts.</string>
    <string name="sport_detail_bowling">Bowling is a precision-based sport that involves rolling a heavy ball down a lane to knock over pins arranged in a triangular formation. The
        objective is to score the highest number of points by knocking down as many pins as possible in each turn. A standard game consists of ten frames,
        with players aiming for strikes (knocking down all pins in one roll) and spares (clearing all pins in two rolls).
        \n\nThe sport is both recreational and competitive, appealing to players of all ages. Bowling requires accuracy, control, and consistency. Players must
        carefully analyze the lane\'s conditions, such as oil patterns, to adjust their technique and achieve the desired trajectory. The balance between
        skill and strategy adds depth to the game.
        \n\nBowling alleys are social hubs where friends and families gather for casual fun. However, professional bowling is a highly competitive field, with
        tournaments like the Professional Bowlers Association (PBA) Tour drawing skilled athletes from around the world. The sport’s universal appeal
        ensures its place as a timeless recreational activity.</string>
    <string name="sport_detail_golf">Golf is a sport of precision, patience, and strategy. Played on expansive courses with varying terrains, the objective is to hit a small ball
        into a series of holes using as few strokes as possible. Each hole presents unique challenges, including bunkers, water hazards, and slopes,
        requiring players to adapt their techniques and strategies.
        \n\nThe game emphasizes mental focus and consistency. Players choose from a range of clubs to execute different shots, such as drives, chips, and putts,
        depending on the distance and terrain. Golfers must also factor in external conditions like wind and weather, adding an element of unpredictability
        to the game.
        \n\nWith prestigious tournaments like The Masters and The Open Championship, golf has a rich history and global following. Iconic players like Tiger
        Woods and Jack Nicklaus have elevated the sport’s profile, inspiring generations of golfers. Golf’s unique combination of skill, strategy, and
        scenic settings make it a favorite among sports enthusiasts.</string>
    <string name="sport_detail_running">Running is one of the most accessible and universal forms of exercise and competition. Whether sprinting over short distances or participating in
        endurance marathons, running tests physical and mental stamina. It is a fundamental activity that forms the basis of many other sports and fitness
        routines.
        \n\nSprint events like the 100-meter dash focus on explosive speed and power, while long-distance running emphasizes endurance and pacing. Runners must
        maintain optimal form and breathing techniques to maximize efficiency and reduce fatigue. Races like marathons and ultramarathons push athletes to
        their physical and psychological limits.
        \n\nBeyond competition, running is celebrated for its health benefits. It improves cardiovascular fitness, strengthens muscles, and releases endorphins,
        often called the "runner's high." As a versatile activity, running attracts people of all ages and fitness levels, making it a cornerstone of
        global fitness culture.</string>
    <string name="sport_detail_soccer">Soccer, also known as football, is the world\’s most popular sport, captivating billions of fans. Played by two teams of eleven players on a
        rectangular field, the objective is to score goals by propelling the ball into the opponent\’s net. Soccer combines skill, strategy, and athleticism,
        making it a truly global phenomenon.
        \n\nThe game is celebrated for its simplicity, requiring only a ball and an open space to play. However, professional soccer demands technical
        excellence, tactical awareness, and teamwork. Players must master dribbling, passing, shooting, and defending, while coaches devise strategies
        to outmaneuver opponents.
        \n\nMajor tournaments like the FIFA World Cup and UEFA Champions League showcase the sport\'s thrilling action and passionate fan culture. Soccer legends
        like Pelé, Diego Maradona, and Lionel Messi have transcended the game, inspiring millions. Its universal appeal and unifying spirit make soccer
        more than just a sport—it’s a way of life.</string>
    <string name="sport_detail_swimming">Swimming is a versatile and demanding sport that tests endurance, speed, and technique. Whether competing in freestyle, backstroke, breaststroke,
        or butterfly, swimmers aim to cover a set distance in the shortest time possible. It is one of the core events in the Olympic Games, drawing global
        attention.
        \n\nThe sport emphasizes efficiency in movement. Swimmers need precise stroke mechanics, strong propulsion, and rhythmic breathing to excel. Training
        often includes intense sessions focusing on technique, strength, and endurance, as well as mental preparation for races.
        \n\nBeyond competition, swimming is a vital life skill and a popular recreational activity. It improves cardiovascular fitness, builds muscle strength,
        and is low-impact, making it accessible to people of all ages. From competitive meets to leisurely swims, the sport’s versatility ensures its
        enduring popularity.</string>
    <string name="sport_detail_table_tennis">Table tennis, also known as ping-pong, is a fast-paced racket sport played on a rectangular table divided by a net. The objective is to score points
        by hitting a lightweight ball over the net and into the opponent’s side of the table. Singles and doubles formats require quick reflexes, precision,
        and strategy.
        \n\nThe sport is known for its rapid exchanges, with top players delivering spins and smashes at incredible speeds. Mastery of spin, placement, and
        timing is essential for success. Table tennis also demands mental agility, as players must anticipate their opponent’s moves and adapt their tactics
        accordingly.
        \n\nPopular worldwide, particularly in Asia and Europe, table tennis is both a recreational pastime and a competitive sport. It is a staple of
        international events like the Olympics and World Championships. Its combination of speed, skill, and accessibility makes table tennis a beloved
        sport across cultures.</string>
    <string name="sport_detail_tennis">Tennis is a sport of precision, power, and strategy, played between two players (singles) or two teams of two (doubles). The objective is to hit
        a ball over the net and into the opponent’s court, aiming to outmaneuver them and win points. Matches are played on various surfaces, including
        grass, clay, and hard courts, each offering unique challenges.
        \n\nPlayers must master a range of shots, including serves, volleys, and groundstrokes, to dominate the game. Physical endurance and mental toughness
        are crucial, as matches can last several hours. Strategy plays a vital role, with players analyzing their opponent’s strengths and weaknesses to
        gain an edge.
        \n\nTennis boasts iconic tournaments like Wimbledon and the US Open, which attract global audiences. Legends such as Serena Williams, Roger Federer,
        and Rafael Nadal have elevated the sport with their exceptional skills and sportsmanship. Tennis continues to inspire players and fans with its
        blend of athleticism and elegance.</string>
    <plurals name="player_count_caption">
        <item quantity="one">1 Player</item>
        <item quantity="other">%1$d Players</item>
    </plurals>
    <string name="olympic_caption">Olympic</string>

    <string name="back_button">Back</string>
</resources>